{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-7",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 7",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "grade5",
    "unit7",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 7: Our favourite school activities",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "activity",
      "answer": "hoạt động",
      "speak": "activity"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "solve",
      "answer": "giải quyết",
      "speak": "solve"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "math",
      "answer": "toán học",
      "speak": "math"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "problem",
      "answer": "vấn đề",
      "speak": "problem"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "project",
      "answer": "dự án",
      "speak": "project"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "game",
      "answer": "trò chơi",
      "speak": "game"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "guitar",
      "answer": "đàn guitar",
      "speak": "guitar"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "group work",
      "answer": "làm việc nhóm",
      "speak": "group work"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "fun",
      "answer": "vui vẻ",
      "speak": "fun"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "interesting",
      "answer": "thú vị",
      "speak": "interesting"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "useful",
      "answer": "hữu ích",
      "speak": "useful"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "enjoy",
      "answer": "tận hưởng",
      "speak": "enjoy"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "draw",
      "answer": "vẽ",
      "speak": "draw"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "paint",
      "answer": "tô màu, vẽ tranh",
      "speak": "paint"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "dance",
      "answer": "nhảy múa",
      "speak": "dance"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "sing",
      "answer": "hát",
      "speak": "sing"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "scientist",
      "answer": "nhà khoa học",
      "speak": "scientist"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "chess",
      "answer": "cờ vua",
      "speak": "chess"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "champion",
      "answer": "nhà vô địch",
      "speak": "champion"
    }
  ]
}